# **STEVIE LYNN MATTHEWS**

4386 W Bronson Lane, Herriman UT 84096 (C) 385-215-5142 stevie.matthews77@gmail.com

## **Summary**

Friendly young woman that is forever enthusiastic about producing a superbly made cup of coffee. With a personable smile and consistent positive attitude I will always be a valuable asset to your team. I always strive to be an excellent leader and problem solver with a resourceful approach when managing a group of individuals in a professional setting or in a hair metal band. Doing so has made me very versatile in any field of work I pursue. While I am consistently molding to new opportunities, challenges, and experiences I am what I consider to be well rounded.

# **Highlights**

- Creative.
- Outstanding social skills.
- Ability to handle fast-paced environments.

- Leadership skills.
- Adaptable.
- Incorporates feedback quickly.
- Types 60 wpm.

# **Experience**

#### The Hair Metal Show, Salt Lake City UT

#### Lead Singer- July 2017 - Current

- Delivers high-energy vocal entertainment to bar patrons consistent with live music guidelines.
- Entertains guests while simultaneously arranging popular music from the 1980's hair metal genre based on audience reactions.
- Completed media interviews on television, radio and local news stations to promote performances.
- Worked closely with directors and fellow performers to identify and perfect optimal performance techniques.
- Successfully delivered 11 outstanding nightly performances the entire duration of The Utah State fair from September 06,2018 September 16,2018.
- Helps prepare stages, move props and break down stages to support smooth productions.

## Experience continued... \

# **STEVIE LYNN MATTHEWS**

#### **Aptive Environmental, Provo UT.**

#### Sales Consultant - November 2019 - September 2020

- Increased sales revenue by skillfully upselling and closing customer sales by driving product benefits around client needs.
- Consulted with long-term, new and prospective customers to understand needs and propose ideal solutions regarding their current pests.
- Explained and reviewed service agreements with customers to cultivate understanding and customer satisfaction.

### The Coffee Shop, Riverton UT.

#### Assistant Manager - September 2018 - September 2019

- Provided leadership and direction for employees, supervising activities to drive productivity and efficiency.
- Kept facility and equipment./l; in good working condition through regular preventive maintenance and repair schedules.
- Implemented training processes for newly hired employees and shift leads.
- Managed weekly inventory and supply tracking, noting items requiring reorder.

#### Barista - October 2016 - September 2018

- Adheres to recipe and presentation standards for specialty coffee drinks.
- Weighs, grinds and packs coffee per customer orders.
- Correctly follows all health, safety and sanitation guidelines.
- Greets and connects with every customer, recommending drinks and pastries.
- Maintains calm demeanor during high-volume periods and special events.

#### Center for Excellence in Higher Education, Murray UT.

#### Admissions Assistant - March 2015 - April 2016

- Served as a central point of contact for potential students and provided information about the college and programs available.
- Coordinated and scheduled appointments for individual student career planning sessions.
- Meticulously entered potential student and service information when scheduling appointments.

# **STEVIE LYNN MATTHEWS**

### **EDUCATION**

**Cameo College of Essential Beauty - Murray, UT** 

#### Diploma - Nail Technician - June 2016

- Trained in state of the art techniques in polishing and treating nails. Served as CND Shellac product line expert.
- Received State Nail Technician License July 2016

**Riverton High School - Riverton, UT** 

#### High School Diploma - Theatre - Jun 2014

 Acting Technique for Film and Advanced Scene Study coursework, Physical theater training, Speech and Theater workshops, Acting and Directing coursework, Character development workshop.

Salt Lake Community College - Remote/ Salt Lake City, UT

#### Certificate - Web Development - January 2021

- Currently developing an understanding of all HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and many other functions regarding web development.
- Gain abilities to combine technical and design skills to create websites from scratch that are compatible with modern day browsers.

## **REFERENCES**

JAMISON FOX - (801)903-8637 RYAN DITTA - (801)656-9627 AUSTIN MERRIL - (801)708-3948 NEPHI ZITTING - (385)225-6534

If you have made it to this point, I humbly thank you for your time and consideration of my candidacy. Have a pleasant day!